Seino
Aim! Zion Ha! Suddenly it's being delivered!
So today we are here at Xevia Arena!
Today is our first time on location!
Yay!
Almost there!
We are here in 5 seconds!
On foot
What are we going to do in this big XEVIA arena today?
Sushimen?
Floating noodles?
Paragliding?
I think it's basketball, isn't it?
That's for sure.
Fruit basket?
Fruit basket? Is that a school?
I don't know. I'm sure we could do all kinds of things.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll be in soon.
Okay? It's about time.
So, yes, I'd like to say hello again to you all.
Yes, I finally got the chance to be on location at Xevia Arena today.
Great!
And for the first time today, all nine of us are here!
Oh, yeah!
Yay!
I don't know if any of you guys know me anymore, but this is the first time all nine of us are here?
Yes, thank you very much.
Here it is.
That's it.
What do you think?
It's great.
I know I made you say that, but...
So, today, the nine of us will be taking on a variety of challenges, so please join us. So, today, the nine of us will be taking on a variety of challenges, so please join us.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Speaking of XEVIA ARENA SENDAI, it is the home of the Sendai Eighty-Niners, which is a well-known team.
Sendai Eighty-Niners, and it is also a place where many artists, both domestic and international, perform live.
It is also a place where many artists, both domestic and international, perform live, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
What kind of place is it for you?
Well, I guess...
It's like a dream stage that you've always dreamed of.
Yes, it is, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
So, today, we're going to be there...
Yes, we're going to set it up.
It's a preliminary inspection, isn't it?
That's right.
Preliminary inspection.
Preliminary inspection, preliminary inspection.
Yes, we will definitely do it here, you know.
Yes, yes.
And today, we're renting out this huge venue for the whole day.
Wow, wow, wow.
That's great.
We're renting it out for a whole day?
Yes, sir.
That's great.
Shall we stay the night?
I'm a big buyer.
It's a big-ticket item.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
We've already got nine people in a large hall today.
So feel free to use it.
Let's take a look at the venue.
Okay.
Let's move.
Let's go.
Let's go! Let's Go
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Go, go, go, go!
I'm right behind you, aren't I?
Don't hold on so tight.
There's a door.
Let's start from the center.
From the center, then boom!
That's great.
Where is it?
Okay, let's do it, ladies and gentlemen.
Okay.
Open the door!
Wow!
Wow.
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
Yeah!
Yoo-hoo!
Ya-hoo!
Thank you!
Are you sure this isn't a lie?
I can see all the guests.
It looks like they're all sitting down.
What do you think of the image of a live show?
In your mind right now...
I really want to be here someday.
I want to stand here someday.
Today, Xebio Arena Sendai
It's a rare chance for us to rent the whole day. This is a rare opportunity to rent out the entire day.
We have prepared a plan like this.
At the dream Xebio Arena Sendai
We are going to play a real 5 game!
special event!
So we have one day to play 5 games!
We have 5 games for you.
Today, we have an individual match.
It's an individual battle.
It's a real battle.
The members will be competing against each other today in individual battles for a chance to win a great prize.
Luxury goods
We asked you in advance what you wanted to get for 30,000 yen.
It's the first time I've been asked.
Do you remember?
It was a very subtle amount of money, 30,000 yen.
It sounded a little realistic, didn't it?
If you said one million yen...
That's true.
It was a dream.
It was quite realistic.
It was embarrassing, wasn't it?
Why the split?
It was pretty spectacular.
Yes, it really was... 30,000 yen.
The results were quite interesting.
What did you say?
One person said she had a dream worth 30,000 yen, just like a cute idol.
And the one who told us what she really wants right now in a very realistic way.
And there was one who told us what she really wants now.
Why did you say that?
If you win, we'll give you a present.
I wish you all the best today.
You're looking good.
Is that everyone?
I don't know what the others wanted.
I don't know. I don't know
Would you like to know?
I'd like to know.
Okay, then. Flip it, please.
Here they are.
Let's start from the left.
Okay.
Pearl Nanasei.
What does Pearl Nanasei want?
An acoustic guitar.
I'd like to be able to stand here in the future.
What can I do for that?
I have to train to play the guitar.
For a musician.
Do you usually play guitar?
No, I don't.
Starting from zero
Starting from zero.
I would like to do my best today as a starting point
Sure, I'll do my best.
Well, then, let's have you do your best.
Next, Ms. Sakura Hinano.
Yes, ma'am.
I wonder...
Ah! It's a fruit platter. I'm an idol.
I can't eat a lot of fruit because it's so expensive.
But I'd like to eat 30,000 yen worth in one day.
What's your favorite fruit, by the way?
I don't know. Right now I like...
Oranges.
Oranges, indeed.
Good luck with oranges!
Next up...
Hikaru Itsuki
What I want is
A 30,000 yen dress.
That's nice.
Did you send her the URL?Did you send them the URL?
I did.
Here it is, please.
I said.
It's pink.
Like lace.
It was too expensive.
I like this one.
It's so cute.
I've always wanted one.
It's a dress, after all.
It's cute.
It sure is.
Date Kahaya-san.
I have a certain famous brand of
Shower head.
It's just 30,000 yen.
It's the only way to go.
It's good for your skin
It makes my hair beautiful.
You're an idol, aren't you?
It's for me.
It's a shower head for me.
Ms. Wada Yasumori
I'm going to give you a belt of a famous brand
I give you a belt of a famous brand
That's great!
Definitely do it!
It starts with a D
I've always wanted one in real life.
But it's only 30,000 yen.
I was feeling like
I'd like to take this opportunity
I'd like to go home today with it in my hand.
I want you to go home with a belt on.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
Next, we have
Ms. Karen Tachibana Karen Tachibana
I chose
Here it is.
Food champlets worth 30,000 yen
Looks amazing, doesn't it?
I love food champions.
I collect them.
But it's so expensive
It's too expensive for me to buy.
I love it.
Like the potato case.
You don't even eat your dinner. You just look at the food churn.
No, no, no, no.
I've been trying to eat.
I've been wanting a curry and rice food champlet.
I want it.
That's what I want.
You want the leftovers?
I'm a big fan of the pre-eaten type.
I love the messy kind.
I love spilled food.
That's nice.
Next, Rie Kitami.
I have about five candidates.
What?
Kitami-san has a panel.
Oh, here it is.
I have
I've decided on the Korean
hair and makeup experience.
Wow!
That's great.
I'm so happy.
It's so popular right now.
YouTubers are doing it.
I wanted to try it.
I wanted to try it once.
This is a good opportunity for me to try it. I asked for this opportunity.
I'm so happy!
Next is Yuta Azuki.
What I want is
a barmuda toaster oven.
Yay!
The Balmuda toaster oven is
really makes bread
Tastes so good that you can't tell the difference
I've heard it said.
You love bread, don't you?
So, if you have a toaster oven in your house
If I had a toaster oven at home
I would be able to eat delicious bread
I really want one.
That's great.
That's the most passionate thing you've ever said.
I really want one.
It's filled with our concerns.
Miu Fujitani, please.
Yes.
30,000 yen worth.
Soft tissues.
I have rhinitis and hay fever.
And hay fever.
It's a family affair.
Everyone's been sniffling all day.
I don't know about that.
That's why the soft tissues
I hesitate.
I chew the snot
That's why I need a soft tissue.
They're a little expensive.
A lot of them for 30,000 yen
I'd like that.
It's for the whole family, right?
The whole family.
So it's really 30,000 yen. So it really is $30,000.
I'm going to round out my materialistic desires.
I'm going to put a stiff price on what I want for all of you.
I really want it.
Yes, you do.
To be honest, yes.
If you say it's for there...
A proper variety.
That's a good idea.
I didn't say anything. He asked if there was anything I wanted for 30,000 yen.
You asked me.
It's what I really want.
We're going to have you fight over what you really want in a five-way competition.
We are pleased to announce the competition.
The competition is here.
What's that?
You're hiding.
Yes, sir.
Five Honiarara and a game of tag.
And obstacle race.
Honiarara Pose Showdown
Paper Balloon Cracking Showdown
20m drop Honyarara catch
Don't drop it!
You can never drop it
Are you interested in any of these?
Who is the demon?
Who is it?
I don't know... a pro.
I hate my legs so much!
I can't do it!
20 meters?
20 meters.
The highest point of the arena is...
That's crazy high.
Who's coming from where?
When I say catch something, you catch a marshmallow. When I say catch something, you catch a marshmallow
The marshmallow catch.
It's the best way to catch marshmallows.
But a 20-meter marshmallow catch...
You can't even see it anymore.
From where?
Each one of these competitions.
Winner
The top three winners
Points
Top 3
First place: 50 points
30 points for 2nd place
10 points for 3rd place
So we will have 5 competitions.
I would like to decide the first place by total
We will decide the winner in total.
Next time notice
or
I'm going to put my greed on the line and ask you all to give me what you really want.
We have 5 contests for you to win.
Start from the monkey's side
Glyphoam and idol scouting photo shoot showdown
Is this okay?
Gachinko Obstacle Race
Let's get started!
Quick, quick, quick!
Karen and Kawaya are fast!
And Mr. Nano!
Oh, you dropped it! You dropped it!
Thank you.
It's not working, is it?
Hey! Hey!
I can't!
It's a smorgasbord.
This is a great game.
I'm gonna go with the group... I'm going to keep the group...
Oh!
I'm going to set it up.
Oops!
This time, it's Kitami-san who's on the attack!
Will he succeed?
Catch a 20-meter marshmallow!
Let's go!
I'm counting on you.
Too bad.
It was so close to my face.
Please.
Please, please, please.
I caught it again.
Excellent.
Good job, sir.